<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jader Dias projects</title>
    <link>http://jaderdias.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jader Dias projects</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 20:04:50 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://jaderdias.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Audio signal one-class classification over the years</title>
      <link>http://jaderdias.github.io/posts/signal-one-class-classification/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 20:04:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jaderdias.github.io/posts/signal-one-class-classification/</guid>
      <description>The first time I encountered the one-class classification of audio di was back in 2009. Back then, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t too keen to try machine learning approaches to the problem, so I stuck to what was familiar to me: convolution. This problem was different from voice recognition because humans can produce a wider range of sounds than the ones I was trying to detect, namely sounds produced by certain insect species.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protect your privacy and security with private and blocking DNS</title>
      <link>http://jaderdias.github.io/posts/use-private-and-blocking-dns/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jaderdias.github.io/posts/use-private-and-blocking-dns/</guid>
      <description>When you’re online on your smartphone, laptop, smart TV, or even when you simply have a WiFi lightbulb, there are many ways your Internet Service Provider (ISP), governments, and companies can track your activities or display ads. The first step towards privacy is to stop using your internet provider’s DNS service and use an encrypted one.
DNS over HTTPS (DoH) and DNS over TLS (DoT) are forms of encryption provided by Google DNS, and Cloudflare DNS, among others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to download Android apps files and analyse them</title>
      <link>http://jaderdias.github.io/posts/download-android-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 13:42:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jaderdias.github.io/posts/download-android-apps/</guid>
      <description>With Apkpure we can download the binaries and resources from any Android application on the Play Store. That’s very interesting if you want to re-use some of its assets.
Suppose you need a list of all the words in English and their translation to Spanish. It could be cumbersome to crawl a translation website or make your app depend on a Translation API for such a task. An alternative is to look for an Android app that has an English to Spanish dictionary and re-use its assets.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>