<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jader Dias projects</title>
    <link>http://jaderdias.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jader Dias projects</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 20:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://jaderdias.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Protect your privacy and security with private and blocking DNS</title>
      <link>http://jaderdias.github.io/posts/use-private-and-blocking-dns/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jaderdias.github.io/posts/use-private-and-blocking-dns/</guid>
      <description>When you&amp;rsquo;re online on your smartphone, laptop, smart TV, or even when you simply have a WiFi lightbulb, there are many ways your Internet Service Provider (ISP), governments, companies and other can track your activities and display ads.
The first step towards privacy is to stop using your internet provider&amp;rsquo;s DNS service and use an encrypted one. DNS over HTTPS (DoH) and DNS over TLS (DoT) are forms of encryption provided by Google DNS, Cloudflare DNS, among others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to download Android apps files and analyse them</title>
      <link>http://jaderdias.github.io/posts/download-android-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 13:42:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jaderdias.github.io/posts/download-android-apps/</guid>
      <description>With Apkpure we can download the binaries and resources from any Android application on the Play Store. That&amp;rsquo;s very interesting if you want to re-use some of its assets.
Suppose you need a list of all the words in English and their translation to Spanish. It could be cumbersome to crawl a translation website or make your app depend on a Translation API for such a task. An alternative is to look for an Android app that has an English to Spanish dictionary and re-use their assets.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
